stupid.com 2014-12-01

# Privacy Policy | Stupid.com

(Last Updated July 31, 2013) (Effective Date August 1, 2013) 

Lotus Internet Corp., Inc. operates the Internet sites Stupid.com, Gaggifts.com, Funnycostume.com, Coolglow.net and Glowsource.com (known as the Sites). Lotus Internet Corp. is committed to protecting the privacy of users of the Sites. This Privacy Statement applies to each of the Sites and describes the information Lotus Internet Corp. collects about users and how that information may be used.

Lotus Internet Corp. reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Statement from time to time. If Lotus Internet Corp. makes material changes to its privacy practices, a prominent notice will be posted on this web page. Each time a user uses the Sites, the current version of the Privacy Statement applies. Accordingly, a user should check the date of this Privacy Statement (which appears at the top) and review for any changes since the last version. If a user does not agree to the Privacy Statement, the user should not use the Sites.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at customerhelp@stupid.com

Notice

Lotus Internet Corp. provides this Privacy Statement to make users aware of Lotus Internet Corp.'s privacy practices, and of the choices a user may make about the way the user's information is collected and used.

Children

Users represent they are of legal age to create binding and financial obligations for any liability users may incur as a result of their use of the Sites. The Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13. Lotus Internet Corp. does not knowingly collect, or wish to obtain, personally identifiable information from children. If Lotus Internet Corp. becomes aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has provided personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental or guardian consent, it will remove user's personally identifiable information from its files. 

What information Lotus Internet Corp. collects

Lotus Internet Corp. may collect three types of information from users of Sites: "personally identifiable information"; "device information" about the device you are using to access our site; and "aggregate information." Personally identifiable information is any piece of information, which can potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a user of the Sites (such as name, email address, postal address, telephone number). Device information is information about the device and its attributes (such as information about how your browser is configured, whether your device has enabled cookies, its Flash settings, the device's identification number and other characteristics about the device); it also may be personally identifiable information in cases where it is associated with the name or other identifier for a Site user. We use device information for purposes such as enhancing the user experience and fraud prevention. Aggregate information is non-personally identifiable/anonymous information about users of the Sites (such as frequency of visits to Sites, Site pages most frequently accessed browser type). Aggregate information also may include pages visited along with any navigation and in-page interactions used during each visit. In-page interactions monitored include: clicks and selections, mouse movement, page scrolling, and form fields focused on (specific keystrokes entered into each field are not collected). Aggregate information is used in a collective manner and no single person can be identified by that compiled information.

We also use Google Analytics for aggregation and analysis of session information. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics, Google has developed a tool that works with major Internet browsers to permit you to opt-out. For more information and install their opt-out tool please visit: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. If you opt-out of Google Analytics, we still may collect some device and aggregate information ourselves through log files as discussed below or in connection with our forms.

On the Sites, users may order products or services, and register to receive materials. Personally identifiable information collected on the Sites includes community forum content, diaries, profiles, photographs, name, unique identifiers (e.g., passwords), contact and billing information (e.g., email address, postal address, telephone, fax), and transaction information.

In order to tailor Lotus Internet Corp.'s subsequent communications to users and continuously improve the Sites' products and services, Lotus Internet Corp. may also ask users to provide information regarding their interests, demographics, experience with its products, and detailed contact preferences. 

Social Network Login

If you chose to use third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook or Twitter, to log into one of our sites that offers that login feature, we may collect information, such as your basic profile information, gender, age, interests, and other demographic and geographical information, from the social networking site you use to interact with our site. If you do not want to share information from your social networking account with us you can either decline to use these features or check your social networking site's current privacy setting options to see what options they provide for limiting disclosures when you use login sharing features.

This privacy policy will apply to our use of information collected about you through these offerings. We do not control the privacy practices of your social networking sites. As a result, we want you to be aware that when you use these offerings you may be providing information to both us and the social networking site, and you should review your social networking site's privacy policy to be sure that you know how it will use any data that it collects. Similarly, if you choose to post content from our site through your social networking accounts, you will be sharing information about your activities with your social networking provider. 

Cookies

Lotus Internet Corp. uses cookies on the Sites. A "browser" or "HTTP" cookie is a unique text file that may be used for data analysis, and enables a web site to tailor information presented to a user based on a user's browsing program. Lotus Internet Corp. may use browser cookies to personalize a user's pages at a Site, to remember a user when the user registers for products or services, for fraud prevention, or to track visits to a Site. If a user does not want Lotus Internet Corp. or its partners to deploy browser cookies in the user's browser when the user visits the Sites, the user may set the browser to reject cookies or to notify the user when a web site tries to place cookies in the browser program. Rejecting cookies may affect a user's ability to use some of the products, features, functions, or services on a Site.

Log Files

Lotus Internet Corp.'s web servers may automatically log aggregate information, such as a user's IP address, domain name, browser type, date and time of access, and other log file data. This information may be used to analyze trends or administer the Sites.

How Lotus Internet Corp. uses the information collected

Lotus Internet Corp. may use the personally identifiable information a user submits for any purposes related to Lotus Internet Corp.'s business, including, but not limited to:

  1. To understand a user's needs and create content that is relevant to the user;
  2. To generate statistical studies;
  3. To conduct market research and planning by sending user surveys;
  4. To notify user referrals of Lotus Internet Corp. services, information, or products when a user requests that Lotus Internet Corp. send such information to referrals;
  5. To improve services, information, and products;
  6. To help a user complete a transaction, or provide services or customer support to users and to recipients of Lotus Internet Corp. products;
  7. To communicate with the user and with recipients of Lotus Internet Corp. products;
  8. To update users and recipients of Lotus Internet Corp. products about services, information, and products;
  9. To personalize a Site for the user;
  10. To notify the user of any changes with a Site which may affect the user;
  11. To enforce terms of use on a Site; and
  12. To allow the user to purchase products, access services, or otherwise engage in activities the user selects.

User names, identifications ("IDs"), and email addresses (as well as any additional information that a user may choose to post) may be publicly available on a Site when a user voluntarily and publicly discloses personally identifiable information, such as when a user posts personally identifiable information in conjunction with a product. Users may not be able to change or remove public postings once posted. Such personally identifiable information may be used by visitors of these pages to send unsolicited messages. Lotus Internet Corp. is not responsible for any consequences which may occur from the use of personally identifiable information that a user chooses to submit to public pages.  
With respect to surveys, in the event that responses are publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey. Lotus Internet Corp. will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users, which as stated earlier is anonymous information that does not identify any specific individual. Circumstances under which Lotus Internet Corp. would publicly disclose such aggregate information include, but are not limited to, sharing survey results with the site population, providing data to Lotus Internet Corp. advertisers on user preferences and/or demographics, and publicizing overall usage data in press communications. Where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where Lotus Internet Corp. advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, Lotus Internet Corp. reserves the right to disclose any information provided by users, provided that no personal information identifying a specific user is disclosed. Participation in surveys is at a user's option; Lotus Internet Corp. does not conduct mandatory surveys.

Gift Certificates

If you choose to send a gift certificate, we will ask you for your recipient's name and email address. The gift certificate will be delivered via email. The Sites store this information for the sole purpose of sending this gift certificate.

Choice/Opt Out

A user makes the decision whether to proceed with activities that request personally identifiable information, such as online contact us and order forms. If a user does not provide requested information, the user may not be able to complete certain transactions.  
Users who use the personally identifiable information of other users agree to use such information only for:

  1. Using services offered through a Site;
  2. Site transaction-related purposes and not for unsolicited commercial messages; or
  3. Other purposes that the other user expressly chooses.

Users are not licensed to add other users to a Site, even users who entered into transactions with them, or to their mail lists without consent.  
Lotus Internet Corp. encourages users to evaluate privacy and security policies of any of the Sites' transaction partners before entering into transactions or choosing to disclose personally identifiable information.

Email

Lotus Internet Corp. will not use the personally identifiable information provided to it online in ways unrelated to the purposes identified in the "How Lotus Internet Corp. Uses Personal Information" section above without first letting a user know and offering the user a choice. If a user no longer wishes to receive direct marketing materials, Lotus Internet Corp. will provide instructions in its marketing email messages on how to be removed from any lists. Lotus Internet Corp. will make commercially reasonable efforts to honor such requests. For information about how Lotus Internet Corp. may share personally identifiable information, please see the Onward Transfer section below.

Email Display

Users may have the opportunity to use a service to send electronic mail to another user or email list. In such cases, a user's valid email address and real name will be included with such messages. In order to prevent abuse, users may not opt out of such a display, but may choose to refrain from using such service to transmit an email message. Lotus Internet Corp. sites may offer an email alias service that allows a user to create an email alias that forwards to the user's personal email account. Lotus Internet Corp. does not publish a user's personal email address, but does publicize email aliases which may allow an individual to identify or contact a user. A user who obtains an email alias may not opt out of such publication of the email alias. Please note, however, in certain cases, such as a "bounced-back" email message, it is possible that the user's personal email address could be exposed to other parties to the communication. 

Photographs

Users may have the opportunity to submit photographs to the Sites for product promotions, contests, and other purposes to be disclosed at the time of request. In these circumstances, the Sites are designed to allow the public to view, download, save, and otherwise access the photographs posted. By submitting a photograph, users waive any privacy expectations users have with respect to the security of such photographs, and Lotus Internet Corp.'s use or exploitation of users' likeness. All photographs submitted to Lotus Internet Corp. become the property of Lotus Internet Corp. and will not be returned.

Onward Transfer

Lotus Internet Corp.'s web servers may automatically log aggregate information, such as a user's IP address, domain name, browser type, date and time of access, and other log file data. This information may be used to analyze trends or administer the Sites.

Log Files

With whom may Lotus Internet Corp. share information:

Unless Lotus Internet Corp. has a user's permission, as otherwise described in this Privacy Statement, or as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, Lotus Internet Corp. will only share the personally identifiable information a user provides online with other entities that are part of the Lotus Internet Corp. corporate family and/or outside service providers who may be used to ship products, process credit cards, provide technical support, handle order processing, or otherwise act on Lotus Internet Corp.'s behalf. These service providers, which may include our affiliates, are prohibited from using users' information for any other purpose, including their own marketing. When Lotus Internet Corp. uses third parties to assist in processing a Site user's personally identifiable information, Lotus Internet Corp. requires that these third parties establish safeguards to protect the confidentiality of the information that we provide them. For processing that involves information subject to Lotus Internet Corp. businesses other than The Sites may share personally identifiable information with third parties for marketing purposes, but will provide users with choices about disclosures of personally identifiable information for marketing purposes. 

The Sites do not share, sell, or rent personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. Please be advised that in certain instances, it may be necessary for Lotus Internet Corp. to disclose a user's personally identifiable information without a user's permission to government officials or otherwise as required by legal obligations. Lotus Internet Corp. may disclose such personally identifiable information when responding to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise legal rights or defend against claims, including fraud or infringement investigations. Data collected online may be combined with information a user provides through other means of communication, such as postal mail or third parties to further carry out the purposes described above under the heading "NOTICE, How Lotus Internet Corp. uses the information collected regarding users". When users choose to provide Lotus Internet Corp. with personally identifiable information, users consent to the transfer and storage of such information by Lotus Internet Corp. servers in the United States. In addition, Lotus Internet Corp. reserves the right to share aggregate information collected from users of the Sites, without prior notice, with entities that are part of the Lotus Internet Corp. corporate family and unrelated third parties. As stated earlier, aggregate information is used in a collective manner and no single person can be identified by such compiled information. Lotus Internet Corp. may make presentations, white papers and other content from other organizations available to the users of Lotus Internet Corp. sites. 

To obtain access to this content you may be asked to provide personal information, such as your name and contact information. This personal information may be shared with the organization that is making the content available and their use of the personal information will be subject to their own privacy policies. If you choose to make information available to other people through instant messages, status updates, group forum discussions or lists, electronic mail messages, bulletin boards, blog postings, or by joining groups or using other networking functions that we may offer on the Sites (either our own or through third party applications such as Facebook, Twitter or Linkedin), this information will be visible to these third parties. Please take care in deciding what information you choose to make available through these mechanisms, as we do not control the manner in which recipients or persons who may see the information may use, retain, or re-disclose the information that you choose to provide. In addition, if you use third party social networking sites to interact with our sites, we may exchange information with those social networking sites. Whether to use social networking sites to interact with our Sites, when that capability is offered, is your choice. In addition, you may restrict the sharing of information from your social networking accounts to the extent permitted by your social networking site's privacy settings. 

Service Orders

To purchase services, users may be asked to be directed to a third party site, like PayPal, to pay for their purchases. If applicable, the third party site may collect payment information directly to facilitate a transaction. None of this information will be captured or stored by Lotus Internet Corp.

Links to third party web sites

Links to third party web sites or widgets to enable sharing of information through social networks on the Sites are provided solely as a convenience to the user. When a user uses these links, the user leaves the Sites. Lotus Internet Corp. has not reviewed all of these third party sites, does not control, and is not responsible for, any of the third party sites, their content or privacy practices. Lotus Internet Corp. does not endorse or make any representations about the third party sites, or any information, services, or products found on the sites. If a user decides to access any of the linked sites, Lotus Internet Corp. encourages the user to read their privacy statements. The user accesses such sites at user's own risk./p>

Bankruptcy or sale of business

Lotus Internet Corp. reserves the right to share or transfer personally identifiable information and aggregate information to a third party should Lotus Internet Corp. ever file for bankruptcy or in the event of a sale, merger or acquisition of Lotus Internet Corp., provided such third party agrees to adhere to the terms of this Privacy Statement.

Data integrity and access

Should a user find inaccuracies in such user's information, or desire to close an account or view or remove the personally identifiable information Lotus Internet Corp. may have regarding the user, the user may contact Lotus Internet Corp. through the communication methods described below, or when technically feasible, directly on a Site. Lotus Internet Corp. will make commercially reasonable efforts to respond to requests for access, updating or removal within thirty (30) days of receiving requests. Lotus Internet Corp. may decline to process users' access, updating or removal requests concerning their personally identifiable information if the requests require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of other users, are inconsistent with our legal obligations, or are impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Security

To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Lotus Internet Corp. implements physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information Lotus Internet Corp. collects. Lotus Internet Corp. uses encryption when using the Internet to transfer or receive requested sensitive personally identifiable information. 

However, Lotus Internet Corp. does not guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never defeat measures taken to prevent improper use of personally identifiable information. Internal Lotus Internet Corp. access to users' nonpublic personally identifiable information is restricted to Lotus Internet Corp.'s administrators and individuals on a need-to-know basis. These individuals are bound by confidentiality agreements. 

User passwords are keys to accounts. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters for passwords and do not disclose passwords to other people in order to prevent loss of account control. Users are responsible for all actions taken in their accounts. Notify Lotus Internet Corp. of any password compromises, and change passwords periodically to maintain account protection. 

Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at customerhelp@stupid.com and we will deactivate your account and will retain and use your information only as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Enforcement

In the event Lotus Internet Corp. becomes aware that the security of a Site has been compromised or user's personally identifiable information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, including but not limited to security attacks or fraud, Lotus Internet Corp. reserves the right to take reasonable appropriate measures, including but not limited to, investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities. 

In the event of a data breach, Lotus Internet Corp. will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals if Lotus Internet Corp. believes that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law. If a user has comments or questions about Lotus Internet Corp.'s privacy statement, please contact: 

Email: customerhelp@stupid.com  
Telephone: 1-877-244-8397.   
Fax: 323-512-7460 

Postal Mail:  
Attn: Lotus Internet Corp. Legal Services - Privacy  
Lotus Internet Corp.  
3301 Barham Blvd Suite 201  
Los Angeles, CA 90068
